{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/900","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"900","name":"Spain Middle/Elementary School","address":"3700 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Detroit Public Schools Communi","licenseNumber":"034934","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.05234,42.35115","geojson":{"id":"900","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.052335763,42.351146121]},"properties":{"name":"Spain Middle/Elementary School","owner":"Detroit Public Schools Communi","address":"3700 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"034934","establishmentid":"900","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"2021-06-08"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4296","name":"Dr. Benjamin Carson HS of Sci & Med","address":"571 Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1700","name":"Friendship Baptist","address":"3900 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622681","name":"Detroit Fitness Foundation","address":"601 Mack","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1639","name":"Children's Hospital of Michigan","address":"3901 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3869","name":"Biggby Coffee","address":"3901 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4996","name":"Children's Hospital of Michigan","address":"3901 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51623124","name":"MMS/DMC Children's Hospital #51728","address":"3901 Beaubian Blvd.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3870","name":"Subway #11819","address":"3901 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"2293","name":"Modern Vending","address":"3901 Beaubien","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5279","name":"Childrens Cafe Stores LLC/Biggby","address":"3901 Beaubien St.","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61601","inspectionDate":"2023-02-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"60409","inspectionDate":"2022-09-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-201.11","violationDescription":"The PERMIT HOLDER shall require FOOD EMPLOYEE applicants and  FOOD EMPLOYEES to report to the PERSON IN CHARGE,  information about their health and activities as they relate to diseases that are transmissible through FOOD. AND report the information in a manner that allows the PERSON IN CHARGE to prevent the likelihood of foodborne disease transmission.(P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Fail to require employees to report illness as rule requires","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Require reporting as stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.18","violationDescription":"The wash, rinse, and SANITIZE solutions shall be maintained clean.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing solutions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Walk-in freezer","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"59409","inspectionDate":"2022-04-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-06-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"56148","inspectionDate":"2021-10-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19 SITE CHECK","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"56170","inspectionDate":"2021-10-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"SERVING LINE","subLocation":"At the Cooler (milk)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-04-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the WALK-IN COOLER","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-04-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54469","inspectionDate":"2021-03-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19 SITE CHECK","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53704","inspectionDate":"2020-11-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53708","inspectionDate":"2020-11-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51520","inspectionDate":"2020-03-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49185","inspectionDate":"2019-09-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"Hot holding cabinet","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-11-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-11-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"47844","inspectionDate":"2019-05-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"43553","inspectionDate":"2018-09-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (milk)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (prep)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (milk)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41973","inspectionDate":"2018-04-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."}]},{"inspectionid":"40171","inspectionDate":"2017-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"38354","inspectionDate":"2017-03-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"37172","inspectionDate":"2016-11-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"900"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}